TRENT SIKKEMA

Platform Engineer

CONTACT

641-780-3293 tsikkema@gmail.com 1702 W 3rd St. Pella, lowa 50219

SKILLS

Server Administration
Automation
Backup Administration
Hardware Support
Continuous Improvement
Disaster Recovery
Problem Solving
Strategic thinking

EDUCATION

Iowa State University

2004-2008

BS in Management Information Systems

PROFILE

Result-driven IT professional with experience in the field of information systems. 10+ years of system administration with a variety of software solutions. Oversaw Windows and Linux servers, Microsoft Exchange including Office 365, and Vmware vSphere. Experience with automation and devop workflows to increase productivity and reduce errors. Always striving to learn new technologies, concepts and ideas.

EXPERIENCE

<u>Platform Engineer (Vermeer Corporation) | 2023 - Current</u>

Develop GitHub processes to deploy applications to Kubernetes. Assist developers with their processes and enable them to develop more efficiently. Develop scripts and automations to maximize productivity.

Senior System Administrator (Vermeer Corporation) | 2013-2023

Supported 300+ Windows and 200+ Linux servers, along with the variety of software on those servers. Managed and migrated Exchange to Office 355. Supported multiple vCenters and 30+ VMware hosts including aging out hardware. On-boarded multiple companies after business acquisitions. Manage backup systems and hardware.

Hardware/Software Analyst (Vermeer Corporation) | 2011-2013

First line problem tickets for end user support, including desktop and printer support.

Server Support Specialist (IBM Global Services) | 2009-2011

Supported problem and change tickets for customers server infrastructure, using Active Directory and other Windows systems.